textabit.com 2012-05-24

# Textabit's Privacy Policy

TEXTABIT values your right to privacy and we are dedicated to protecting it. This Privacy Policy applies to all personally identifiable information that we collect from you in providing the TEXTABIT service ("Service") or your use of this website ("Site"). If you have received a message from a user of TEXTABIT, the relevant privacy policy will be that made available by the user. 

**Information we collect**  
TEXTABIT only collects personal information about you from our Site if you choose to provide it to us. You can visit the Site without revealing any personally identifiable information. In order to use the Services you will be asked to register or provide identifiable information. 

**Updating and accessing your Information**  
TEXTABIT uses its best endeavors to ensure that the information it obtains is accurate, complete and up to date. You may access or change information that TEXTABIT has collected about you by accessing your account online or placing your request in writing and sending your request to us at the address below: 

Email: support@textabit.com or via mail:   
Attn: Privacy Department  
TEXTABIT  
26 Park Street Suite 2044  
Montclair New Jersey 07042  
Please allow 15 days for your request to be processed 

**Data Security**  
TEXTABIT will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information that we hold about you. TEXTABIT has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, TEXTABIT cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail provided we have your e-mail address.

**Use and Disclosure of Your Information**  
The personal information collected by TEXTABIT is used to sign you up and deliver the Service or to deliver features, notices, administration and services as part of the Site. We do not disclose or market personal information obtained through the Site to others unless (a) it is to complete a transaction that you initiate, (b) it is required by law, (c) disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of customers, employees, or property, (d) you specifically authorize it or (e) it is required in order to service the company's system infrastructure. The personal information collected by TEXTABIT as part of registering for TEXTABIT is used to ensure that the Services are delivered to you and that you are advised of any possible information that may relate to your account. TEXTABIT collects personal financial information to confirm the identity of users and bill customers for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as membership or credit card numbers) are collected from you to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. We will not share financial or unique identifier information with third parties without your prior consent. When you sign up for the TEXTABIT Service your consent is required to provide your financial or contact information to those third parties necessary to process your transactions with us, such as credit card companies. TEXTABIT will not use or disclose this information in any way, other than that disclosed in this policy. 

**Contributed Content**  
The Site may provide users at various times with the ability to ask questions in a public forum or provide Content. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Specific Technology Usage**  
You may have heard about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver content, and to record registration and personalization information. We use your IP address to audit behavior and to help diagnose problems with our Services, and to administer the Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you. If you do not wish to receive any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly.

**Third Party Website Links**  
TEXTABIT provides links to web sites outside of the Site. These linked sites are not under the control of TEXTABIT, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of companies linked to our Site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, you should check the privacy policies of those external web sites carefully. 

**Modifications & Questions**  
We may modify this policy from time to time, so please check back to ensure that any changes are acceptable to you. TEXTABIT reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on its web site. Your continued use of the Site indicates that you accept the policy in place at that time. Please note that in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or similar corporate reorganization we may transfer personal information to another corporate entity. In the event that this occurs, your personal information will in every other respect remain under the same privacy policy. 

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact us:

Email: support@textabit.com or via mail:   
Attn: Privacy Department  
TEXTABIT  
26 Park Street Suite 2044  
Montclair New Jersey 07042  
Please allow 15 days for any request to be processed
